Subtitle Provide by kisskh.org Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم kisskh.org [Admin.@YNG]
["Boombayah" by BLACKPINK playing]
[أغنية "بومبايا" من بلاك بينك تُعزف]
[effervescent, upbeat pop music continues]
[تستمر موسيقى البوب ​​​​الفوارة والمبهجة]
♪ BLACKPINK in your area ♪
♪ بلاك بينك في منطقتك ♪
♪ Been a bad girl, I know I am ♪
♪ لقد كنت فتاة سيئة، وأنا أعلم أنني كذلك ♪
♪ And I'm so hot, I need a fan ♪
♪ وأنا حار جدًا، أحتاج إلى مروحة ♪
♪ I don't want a boy, I need a man ♪
♪ أنا لا أريد ولدًا، أنا بحاجة إلى رجل ♪
♪ Click-clack! Badda-bing, badda-boom ♪
♪ طقطقة! صوت البحر، دوي البحر ♪
[BLACKPINK continue singing in Korean]
[BLACKPINK يستمرون في الغناء باللغة الكورية]
[song trails off]
[تنتهي الأغنية]
[Enid] Admit it.
[إينيد] اعترف بذلك.
This is the Wednesday Addams you didn't know you needed.
هذه هي الأربعاء آدامز التي لم تكن تعلم أنك بحاجة إليها.
[jauntily macabre intro music playing]
[موسيقى مقدمة مرحة ومرعبة تُعزف]
[intro trails off]
[مقدمة تنتهي]
[dour music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى كئيبة]
I warned you about Tyler coming.
لقد حذرتك من قدوم تايلر.
I told you to cancel the remembrance procession.
لقد طلبت منك إلغاء مسيرة الذكرى.
What's your part in all of this?
ما هو دورك في كل هذا؟
I lured Tyler away from the ceremony.
لقد أغريت تايلر بعيدًا عن الحفل.
Wednesday had a plan to control him.
كان لدى الأربعاء خطة للسيطرة عليه.
It did not go well.
لم تسير الأمور على ما يرام.
My plan was unfolding with the precision of a Swiss watch.
كانت خطتي تتكشف بدقة ساعة سويسرية.
Until that second Hyde showed up and smashed the watch.
حتى ظهر هايد للمرة الثانية وحطم الساعة.
[Dort] Two Hydes?
[دورت] اثنان هايد؟
You're dismissed.
لقد تم طردك.
The second monster, who the hell's that?
الوحش الثاني، من هو هذا الوحش؟
Francoise Galpin, Tyler's mother.
فرانسواز جالبين، والدة تايلر.
She's been dead for 15 years.
لقد ماتت منذ 15 عامًا.
I was at her funeral.
كنت في جنازتها.
Augustus Stonehurst faked Francoise's death.
أوغسطس ستونهرست زور موت فرانسواز.
He was experimenting on her and others in the basement of Willow Hill.
كان يجري تجاربه عليها وعلى الآخرين في قبو ويلو هيل.
His daughter Judi never wanted you to find out.
ابنته جودي لم تكن تريد أن تكتشف ذلك أبدًا.
- [Santiago] Judi's been reported missing. - Wow.
- [سانتياغو] تم الإبلاغ عن اختفاء جودي. - واو.
Why am I only hearing about this now?
لماذا أسمع عن هذا الآن فقط؟
Francoise and Tyler are gone,
لقد رحل فرانسواز وتايلر،
with no plans to return to Jericho.
بدون أي خطط للعودة إلى أريحا.
Francoise gave me her word, and I believe her.
لقد أعطتني فرانسواز كلمتها، وأنا أصدقها.
[Santiago scoffs] Hmm.
[سانتياغو يسخر] همم.
Sounds like our problem solved itself.
يبدو أن مشكلتنا قد حلت نفسها.
I should arrest you right here for aiding and abetting a murderer.
يجب أن أعتقلك هنا بتهمة المساعدة والتحريض على القاتل.
I make no apologies for my actions.
لا أقدم أي اعتذار عن أفعالي.
You ordered your deputies to abandon the school
لقد أمرت نوابك بالتخلي عن المدرسة
so they could save Normies at Pilgrim World.
حتى يتمكنوا من إنقاذ الأشخاص العاديين في عالم الحجاج.
Leaving Outcasts to fend for themselves? How do you think the press will take that?
ترك المنبوذين ليتدبروا أمرهم بأنفسهم؟ كيف تتوقع أن تتقبل الصحافة هذا الأمر؟
[Dort] Luckily, no one got hurt,
[دورت] لحسن الحظ، لم يصب أحد بأذى،
but in an abundance of caution I am mandating a school-wide curfew.
ولكن من باب الحيطة والحذر، قررت فرض حظر تجول على مستوى المدرسة.
Our gala is around the corner. So why don't we all just take the win?
حفلنا على الأبواب. فلماذا لا نفرح جميعًا بالفوز؟
Wherever there's murder and mayhem,
أينما كان هناك القتل والفوضى،
you'll always find an Addams.
ستجد دائمًا آدامز.
With corpse bells on.
مع أجراس الجثث.
[jarring music building]
[بناء موسيقى مزعجة]
[music swells]
[تتضخم الموسيقى]
[slow clapping]
[تصفيق بطيء]
Bravo, Miss Addams.
برافو، الآنسة آدامز.
You managed to release not one, but two Hydes from the asylum.
لقد تمكنت من إطلاق سراح ليس واحدًا، بل اثنين من هايد من اللجوء.
I was hoping once Day of the Dead was over,
كنت أتمنى أن ينتهي يوم الموتى،
you would sashay back into the afterlife.
سوف تعود مسرعا إلى الحياة الآخرة.
I don't sashay.
أنا لا أتمايل.
Ever.
أبدًا.
Are the Galpins still in Jericho?
هل لا يزال الغالبين في أريحا؟
Now I'm adding bloodhound to my resume?
الآن أقوم بإضافة كلب الصيد إلى سيرتي الذاتية؟
You're my spirit guide.
أنت مرشدي الروحي.
How about some actual guidance?
ماذا عن بعض التوجيهات الفعلية؟
I can tell you your vision hasn't changed.
أستطيع أن أقول لك أن رؤيتك لم تتغير.
Enid still dies, and you are still responsible.
لا تزال إينيد تموت، وأنت لا تزال المسؤول.
What do I need to do?
ماذا يجب أن أفعل؟
Finally, some positive engagement.
وأخيرا، بعض المشاركة الإيجابية.
[exhales]
[يزفر]
Your psychic ability isn't just inherited.
قدراتك النفسية ليست موروثة فقط.
It's intricately tied to your familial bonds.
إنه مرتبط بشكل معقد بروابطك العائلية.
The escalating and unresolved tension with your mother
التوتر المتصاعد وغير المحلول مع والدتك
is what's disrupting your power.
هو ما يعطل قوتك.
That's absurd.
هذا سخيف.
The Addams family lineage has always drawn strength
لقد استمدت عائلة آدامز قوتها دائمًا
from the unity of its members.
من وحدة أعضائها.
Like it or not,
سواء أعجبك ذلك أم لا،
you are part of that spiritual heritage.
أنت جزء من هذا التراث الروحي.
But that strength demands emotional clarity.
لكن هذه القوة تتطلب الوضوح العاطفي.
I don't need to deal with any emotions,
لا أحتاج إلى التعامل مع أي مشاعر،
and I don't need to cater
ولا أحتاج إلى تلبية
to my mother's maudlin need to insert herself into my life.
إلى حاجة والدتي العاطفية لإدخال نفسها في حياتي.
Your lack of empathy is what makes you the weak link,
إن افتقارك للتعاطف هو ما يجعلك الحلقة الضعيفة،
spiritually speaking.
روحيا.
I'm the only link that matters.
أنا الرابط الوحيد الذي يهم.
Leave Tyler and Francoise to the authorities.
اترك تايلر وفرانسواز للسلطات.
Focus on fixing the relationship with your mother.
ركز على إصلاح علاقتك مع والدتك.
Miss Addams, who are you talking to?
السيدة آدامز، من الذي تتحدثين معه؟
Professor,
أستاذ،
did you ever teach Francoise Galpin?
هل سبق لك أن قمت بتدريس فرانسواز جالبين؟
[gulps]
[بلع]
She was Francoise Night in those days.
كانت تُدعى فرانسواز نايت في تلك الأيام.
But science didn't hold her interest, unlike her brother.
لكن العلم لم يحظى باهتمامها، على عكس أخيها.
Francoise had a brother?
هل كان لدى فرانسواز أخ؟
Isaac.
إسحاق.
He was the most brilliant DaVinci I've ever met.
لقد كان دافينشي الأكثر ذكاءً الذي قابلته على الإطلاق.
I owe him my life.
أنا مدين له بحياتي.
He designed this life-support system for me.
لقد صمم هذا النظام لدعم حياتي.
You two must have been close.
لا بد أنكما كنتما قريبين من بعضكما.
Ha. Ha!
هاها. هاها!
Isaac didn't care about people,
لم يكن إسحاق يهتم بالناس،
but he loved to play God.
لكنّه أحبّ أن يلعب دور الله.
You said DaVincis loved Augustus Stonehurst.
لقد قلت أن دافنشي أحب أوغسطس ستونهورست.
Was Isaac one of his students?
فهل كان إسحاق أحد تلاميذه؟
Stonehurst was his mentor.
وكان ستونهورست معلمه.
He built Isaac that secret lab at Iago Tower.
لقد بنى لإسحاق ذلك المختبر السري في برج ياغو.
They were thick as thieves.
لقد كانوا كاللصوص.
Until the night the lab exploded.
حتى الليلة التي انفجر فيها المختبر.
What happened to Isaac?
ماذا حدث لإسحاق؟
His body was never found.
ولم يتم العثور على جثته أبدًا.
Some say he ran away,
ويقول البعض أنه هرب،
others... that he's buried under the Skull Tree.
الآخرين... أنه مدفون تحت شجرة الجمجمة.
That's just an urban legend, but you're welcome to try and dig him up.
إنها مجرد أسطورة حضرية، ولكن يمكنك محاولة استخراجها.
[tense, jittery music playing]
[موسيقى متوترة ومتوترة]
I'm running a special on the answers for Tudor-Pole's math quiz.
أقوم بإجراء عرض خاص على إجابات اختبار الرياضيات الخاص بـ Tudor-Pole.
How much?
كم ثمن؟
Five bucks. Guaranteed A, or your money back.
خمسة دولارات. ضمان A، أو استرداد أموالك.
[music halts]
[توقف الموسيقى]
Store's closed.
المتجر مغلق.
Everybody out.
الجميع خارجا.
[students grumbling]
[تذمر الطلاب]
Your zombie. When's the last time you saw him?
زومبي الخاص بك. متى كانت آخر مرة رأيته؟
You know my waterboard is in my closet.
أنت تعرف أن لوح الماء الخاص بي موجود في خزانتي.
Right next to her skeletons.
بجوار هياكلها العظمية مباشرة.
[threatening music rises, fades]
[ترتفع الموسيقى المهددة، ثم تتلاشى]
I saw him at Pilgrim World, okay?
لقد رأيته في عالم الحجاج، حسنًا؟
But Slurp's gone now. For good.
لكن سلورب رحل الآن، للأبد.
His name is Isaac Night.
اسمه اسحق نايت.
Isaac Night?
إسحاق نايت؟
And how do you know he's gone?
وكيف تعرف أنه رحل؟
I might have let him go.
ربما كنت سأتركه يذهب.
Don't tell Dad.
لا تخبر أبي.
I kind of lied to him.
لقد كذبت عليه نوعا ما.
What a bold move for somebody who has no poker face.
يا لها من خطوة جريئة لشخص لا يملك وجهًا جامدًا.
You think he knows?
هل تعتقد أنه يعرف؟
Dig up everything you can find on Isaac Night.
ابحث عن كل ما يمكنك العثور عليه في ليلة إسحاق.
He's just trying to live his life now that he's got a second chance.
إنه يحاول فقط أن يعيش حياته الآن بعد أن حصل على فرصة ثانية.
Your heart is as soft as your skull.
قلبك ناعم مثل جمجمتك.
Can your pea brain remember anything else?
هل يستطيع دماغك الصغير أن يتذكر أي شيء آخر؟
He dropped this.
لقد أسقط هذا.
[unsettling music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مزعجة]
He's looking for his sister.
إنه يبحث عن أخته.
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
Hey.
يا.
You sleep well?
هل تنام جيدا؟
I'm really here.
أنا هنا حقا.
Your father built this place after you were born.
لقد بنى والدك هذا المكان بعد ولادتك.
He wanted some place close to keep you safe in case I, uh...
لقد أراد مكانًا قريبًا ليبقيك آمنًا في حالة ما إذا، آه...
Well, you know.
حسنا، أنت تعرف.
I remember your funeral like it was yesterday.
أتذكر جنازتك وكأنها حدثت بالأمس.
Dr. Stonehurst lied to your father.
لقد كذب الدكتور ستونهورست على والدك.
To everybody.
الى الجميع.
[metallic rattling]
[خشخشة معدنية]
- You don't trust me? - You unleashed your Hyde last night.
- أنت لا تثق بي؟ - لقد أطلقت العنان لهايد الخاص بك الليلة الماضية.
That's something you just don't recover from overnight.
هذا شيء لا يمكنك التعافي منه بين عشية وضحاها.
It... It was because you didn't have a master.
لقد كان ذلك... لأنه لم يكن لديك سيد.
So you're my master now?
إذن أنت سيدي الآن؟
Mm-hmm.
مممم.
Well, you must be hungry.
حسنًا، لا بد أنك جائع.
[coughing violently]
[السعال بعنف]
Do you want some, uh, pancakes?
هل تريد بعض الفطائر؟
They were always your favorite, right?
لقد كانوا دائمًا المفضلين لديك، أليس كذلك؟
I'm not a kid anymore, so stop trying to placate me.
أنا لم أعد طفلاً بعد الآن، لذا توقف عن محاولة استرضائي.
- [grunts] - [Tyler groans]
- [يئن] - [يئن تايلر]
Never raise your voice to me again.
لا ترفع صوتك علي مرة أخرى.
Now I'm... I'm going to make you those pancakes.
الآن أنا... سأصنع لك تلك الفطائر.
Sweetie.
حبيبي.
You okay?
هل انت بخير؟
Yeah. Sorry.
نعم، آسف.
Just didn't sleep very much.
لم أنم كثيرا.
[sighs] You did just face off with a Hyde.
[تنهد] لقد واجهت للتو هايد.
Yeah. I'm sure that's it.
نعم، أنا متأكد من ذلك.
[phone chiming, buzzing]
[رنين الهاتف، طنين]
Your mom again?
والدتك مرة أخرى؟
[sighs]
[تنهدات]
[Enid] She's been calling a lot recently.
[إينيد] لقد كانت تتصل كثيرًا في الآونة الأخيرة.
Family drama back home. I'll call her later.
دراما عائلية في الوطن. سأتصل بها لاحقًا.
You know you can talk to me about that stuff.
أنت تعلم أنك تستطيع التحدث معي حول هذا الموضوع.
Some things words can't fix.
بعض الأشياء لا يمكن للكلمات إصلاحها.
[gentle music playing]
[عزف موسيقى هادئة]
[Capri clears throat]
[كابري يصفى حلقه]
Professor Capri. I was just checking on Enid.
أستاذة كابري. كنتُ أطمئن على إينيد.
I'm sure Enid's lips are fine.
أنا متأكد من أن شفاه إينيد بخير.
You know boys aren't allowed in the girls' dorm solo.
أنت تعلم أنه لا يُسمح للأولاد بالدخول إلى سكن الفتيات بمفردهم.
Want to tell me what happened last night?
هل تريد أن تخبرني ماذا حدث الليلة الماضية؟
I know. We should have told somebody about the Hyde.
أعرف. كان ينبغي أن نخبر أحدًا عن هايد.
No. Not that. What happened after.
لا، ليس هذا. ما حدث بعد ذلك.
In the music room.
في غرفة الموسيقى.
[sighs softly] I don't know what you're talking about.
[يتنهد بهدوء] لا أعرف عما تتحدث.
Enid, you transformed into a werewolf.
إينيد، لقد تحولت إلى مستذئب.
Without a full moon. I saw you.
بدون اكتمال القمر، رأيتك.
[delicate, introspective music playing]
[عزف موسيقى رقيقة وتأملية]
Enid, it's okay.
إينيد، لا بأس.
It... It means you could be an Alpha.
هذا... هذا يعني أنه بإمكانك أن تكون ألفا.
[Enid gasps]
[تشهق إينيد]
Wait. Me?
انتظر. انا؟
We don't know, but look at the facts.
نحن لا نعلم، ولكن انظر إلى الحقائق.
You're a late bloomer.
أنت تتأخر في التفتح.
The first time you wolfed out was under a blood moon, correct?
المرة الأولى التي تناولت فيها الطعام كانت تحت ضوء القمر الدموي، أليس كذلك؟
Those are all classic signs of a potential Alpha.
تلك كلها علامات كلاسيكية لألفا محتمل.
They're the strongest of our kind. Very rare.
إنهم الأقوى بيننا. نادرون جدًا.
If you are one, we have to manage it.
إذا كنت واحدًا منهم، فيجب علينا إدارته.
[phone buzzing]
[رنين الهاتف]
But don't Alphas normally end up alone?
لكن ألا ينتهي الأمر عادةً بالألفا بمفردهم؟
Sorry. One minute. It's Principal Dort.
عذراً. لحظة. أنا المدير دورت.
We're implementing a new curfew.
نحن نطبق حظر تجوال جديد.
After dinner, everyone's confined to their rooms.
بعد العشاء، الجميع محصورون في غرفهم.
Anyone fails to comply, barred... from the gala...
كل من يفشل في الامتثال، سيتم منعه... من الحفل...
Oh, Enid.
أوه، إينيد.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
There's a lot of misinformation out there
هناك الكثير من المعلومات المضللة هناك
about Alphas becoming lone wolves,
حول تحول الألفا إلى ذئاب منفردة،
but as long as we get this under control, there's nothing to worry about.
ولكن طالما تمكنا من السيطرة على هذا الأمر، فلا داعي للقلق.
Okay?
تمام؟
[music growing fearful]
[موسيقى مخيفة]
[breathing shakily]
[يتنفس بصعوبة]
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
Pull.
يحذب.
[Hester] Wednesday.
[هستر] الأربعاء.
What brings you all this way on such a dreadful day?
ما الذي أتى بك إلى هنا في مثل هذا اليوم الرهيب؟
I need help restoring my psychic ability.
أحتاج إلى مساعدة لاستعادة قدرتي النفسية.
The last time I intervened, your mother burned that spell book.
آخر مرة تدخلت فيها، أحرقت والدتك كتاب التعويذة هذا.
Yes, but you're a Raven.
نعم، ولكنك غراب.
You must know another way.
يجب أن تعرف طريقة أخرى.
Pull.
يحذب.
Every now and then,
من وقت لآخر،
I crank up my psychic sight so I can spy on old enemies.
أقوم بتفعيل قدراتي النفسية حتى أتمكن من التجسس على الأعداء القدامى.
Just a few flashes of their suffering. Usually brightens my mood.
لمحاتٌ قليلةٌ من معاناتهم. عادةً ما تُبهجُ مزاجي.
You stopped using it after what happened to Aunt Ophelia.
لقد توقفت عن استخدامه بعد ما حدث لعمتك أوفليا.
Is that what your mother told you?
هل هذا ما قالته لك والدتك؟
Doves can be so emotional,
يمكن أن تكون الحمائم عاطفية جدًا،
always living in the past and wallowing in their feelings.
الذين يعيشون دائمًا في الماضي ويتخبطون في مشاعرهم.
I made a choice to leave all that behind.
لقد اخترت أن أترك كل ذلك خلفي.
Women like us can't be burdened by family.
لا يمكن للنساء مثلنا أن يتحملن أعباء الأسرة.
We forge our own path, dig our own grave.
نحن نصنع طريقنا بأنفسنا، ونحفر قبرنا بأنفسنا.
This is one of the Hydes I accidentally released at Willow Hill.
هذا هو أحد الهايدز الذي أطلقته عن طريق الخطأ في ويلو هيل.
I need to find her.
أحتاج إلى العثور عليها.
[suspicious music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مشبوهة]
Have you ever come across the name Rosaline Rotwood?
هل سبق لك أن صادفت اسم روزالين روتوود؟
Professor Rotwood was a legendary Raven.
كان البروفيسور روتوود غرابًا أسطوريًا.
She taught runes and ancient cryptology during my time at Nevermore.
لقد قامت بتدريس الأحرف الرونية والتشفير القديم أثناء وجودي في Nevermore.
I was an amateur tomb raider,
لقد كنت من هواة نبش القبور،
so I took to that class like a leech to blood.
لذا فقد التحقت بتلك الفئة مثل علقة للدم.
In fact, your parents are slumming in her old cottage.
في الواقع، والديك يعيشون في كوخها القديم.
She used to hold secret soirées in her seance chamber.
كانت تعقد أمسيات سرية في غرفة جلساتها الروحانية.
She may have served stale sherry,
ربما تكون قد قدمت شيري قديمًا،
but her psychic sight was extraordinary.
لكن قدرتها على الرؤية كانت غير عادية.
What does this have to do with my situation?
ما علاقة هذا بحالتي؟
Rotwood is buried in the Nevermore graveyard.
تم دفن روتوود في مقبرة نيفرمور.
Her headstone is imbued with her dark energy.
حجر قبرها مشبع بطاقتها المظلمة.
If a Raven recites the inscription etched underneath,
إذا تلا الغراب النقش المحفور في الأسفل،
you will be granted temporary sight.
سيتم منحك رؤية مؤقتة.
Thank you, Grandmama.
شكرا لك يا جدتي.
I'm the last person to offer advice, and you're the last person to accept any,
أنا آخر شخص يقدم النصيحة، وأنت آخر شخص يقبل أي نصيحة.
but... proceed with caution, my dear.
لكن... تعامل بحذر، عزيزتي.
Pull.
يحذب.
[bird squawks]
[صرخات الطيور]
Aw.
أوه.
Oh, there you are.
أوه، أنت هناك.
Dort turned dinner into a campus safety TED talk.
حول دورت العشاء إلى محاضرة TED حول سلامة الحرم الجامعي.
Ugh, I had to escape.
آه، كان عليّ الهروب.
- Where are you charging off to? - The Nevermore graveyard.
- إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟ - مقبرة نيفرمور.
Hello? Curfew!
مرحبا؟ حظر التجوال!
If you're not back, the entire dorm is gonna be barred from the gala.
إذا لم تعد، سيتم منع السكن بأكمله من حضور الحفل.
You may have dropped out of the orchestra,
ربما تكون قد انسحبت من الأوركسترا،
but I've been rehearsing my dance routine for weeks.
لكنني كنت أتدرب على روتين الرقص الخاص بي لأسابيع.
I'm not cowering away in the room while Tyler and his mother are out there.
أنا لا أختبئ في الغرفة بينما تايلر وأمه في الخارج.
I'm going to find them.
سأذهب للعثور عليهم.
How exactly?
كيف بالضبط؟
That's on a need-to-know basis. After last night, you don't need to know.
هذا أمرٌ ضروري. بعد الليلة الماضية، لستَ بحاجةٍ للمعرفة.
Did it ever occur to you that we're all just trying our best?
هل خطر ببالك يومًا أننا جميعًا نحاول أن نبذل قصارى جهدنا؟
Trying your best means you're planning on failing and letting me know in advance.
إن بذل قصارى جهدك يعني أنك تخطط للفشل وإخباري بذلك مسبقًا.
The fact that you can be so arrogant
حقيقة أنك يمكن أن تكون مغرورًا جدًا
and still make so many bad decisions is staggering.
وما زالوا يتخذون الكثير من القرارات السيئة، وهذا أمر مذهل.
How was I supposed to know that Tyler's mother was still alive?
كيف كان من المفترض أن أعرف أن والدة تايلر لا تزال على قيد الحياة؟
You weren't! That's the whole point.
لم تكن كذلك! هذه هي النقطة الأساسية.
Your arsonist-slash-firefighter complex is right there in black and white.
مجمع الحريق-الحرق-رجل الإطفاء الخاص بك موجود هناك باللونين الأسود والأبيض.
You unleash chaos just so you can stamp it out and then feel superior.
أنت تطلق العنان للفوضى فقط حتى تتمكن من القضاء عليها ثم تشعر بالتفوق.
You think you're powerful now because you finally wolfed out?
هل تعتقد أنك قوي الآن لأنك استسلمت أخيرًا؟
[breathing tremulously] You have no idea what I'm capable of.
[يتنفس بشكل مرتجف] ليس لديك أي فكرة عما أنا قادر على فعله.
Now who sounds arrogant?
الآن من الذي يبدو متغطرسًا؟
Have you ever put yourself in someone else's shoes to see how they felt?
هل وضعت نفسك في مكان شخص آخر لترى كيف يشعر؟
My shoes are filled with broken glass and razor blades.
كانت أحذيتي مليئة بالزجاج المكسور وشفرات الحلاقة.
You'd bleed out after two steps.
سوف تنزف بعد خطوتين.
[somber, melancholy music playing]
[موسيقى حزينة وكئيبة تعزف]
[chilling music builds]
[تتصاعد الموسيقى المرعبة]
Capri's going house-to-house doing dorm checks?
هل تذهب كابري من منزل إلى منزل لتفقد السكن؟
How long until she gets up here?
كم من الوقت حتى تصل إلى هنا؟
That's barely enough time to make it to the graveyard and back.
هذا بالكاد وقت كافٍ للوصول إلى المقبرة والعودة.
I am not missing that gala!
أنا لا أفتقد هذا الحفل!
I will literally drag Wednesday back by her braids if I have to!
سأسحب الأربعاء حرفيًا من ضفائرها إذا اضطررت إلى ذلك!
[dour, foreboding music playing]
[موسيقى كئيبة ومخيفة تعزف]
[Wednesday] "In the Raven's shadow,
[الأربعاء] "في ظل الغراب،
grant me use of your ephemeral sight."
"أعطني استخدام رؤيتك الزائلة."
"Be warned. Should my gaze be broken, a deadly trick I will play."
"احذر. إذا انكسر نظري، سألعب خدعة قاتلة."
[chanting in Latin]
[ترديد باللاتينية]
[harrowing music spikes]
[ارتفاعات موسيقية مروعة]
[gasp echoing]
[صدى شهقة]
How dare you enter my chamber uninvited?
كيف تجرؤ على دخول غرفتي دون دعوة؟
I'm a Raven.
أنا الغراب.
One whose wings have been clipped.
الذي تم قص أجنحته.
My grandmother told me that if I read the inscription on your grave,
قالت لي جدتي أنه إذا قرأت النقش على قبرك،
you would grant me second sight.
سوف تمنحني رؤية ثانية.
[chuckles]
[يضحك]
Hester.
هيستر.
So desperate for my approval.
يائسة جدًا للحصول على موافقتي.
But she never had what it took to be a truly great Raven.
لكنها لم تمتلك أبدًا ما يلزم لتصبح غرابًا عظيمًا حقًا.
She craved a family so badly, she fell head over heels with a huckster.
لقد كانت تتوق إلى عائلة بشدة، حتى أنها وقعت في غرام أحد المحتالين.
I sense none of that sentimentality in you.
لا أشعر بأي من تلك المشاعر فيك.
No. The crack in your monochrome armor is
لا. الشق في درعك أحادي اللون هو
overbearing arrogance.
الغطرسة المتغطرسة.
You positively reek of the stuff.
أنت بالتأكيد تنبعث منك رائحة هذه الأشياء.
Tyler and Francoise Galpin.
تايلر وفرانسواز جالبين.
I need to find them.
أريد أن أجدهم.
There's no time to waste. A life hangs in the balance.
لا وقتَ لإضاعته. الحياةُ على المحك.
What are you willing to endure to excavate the truth?
ما الذي أنت على استعداد لتحمله من أجل اكتشاف الحقيقة؟
Hold your hand over the flame,
ضع يدك فوق اللهب،
and your psychic sight will be temporarily renewed.
وسوف تتجدد رؤيتك النفسية مؤقتًا.
But beware.
ولكن احذر.
If you pull your palm from the flame,
إذا سحبت راحة يدك من اللهب،
you will break the Raven's gaze, and...
ستكسر نظرة الغراب، و...
there will be a price to pay.
سيكون هناك ثمن يجب دفعه.
[suspenseful music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مشوقة]
[Enid, faintly] Wednesday, where are you?
[إينيد، بصوت خافت] الأربعاء، أين أنت؟
[Enid, echoing] Wednesday!
[إينيد، تردد صدى] الأربعاء!
We have to go back!
علينا أن نعود!
[Rotwood] There will be a price to pay.
[روتوود] سيكون هناك ثمن يجب دفعه.
[both exhale]
[كلاهما يزفر]
No.
لا.
- No, no, no, no, no. - [shrieking]
- لا، لا، لا، لا، لا. - [صراخ]
[Wednesday] Enid?
[الأربعاء] إينيد؟
What the hell happened to me?
ماذا حدث لي؟
[morbidly intriguing music playing]
[عزف موسيقى مثيرة للاهتمام بشكل مرضي]
Why am I staring at...
لماذا أنا أتطلع إلى...؟
me?
أنا؟
Because we've somehow swapped bodies.
لأننا قمنا بتبديل الأجساد بطريقة ما.
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
We were at the graveyard, and now we're here, and now it's morning.
كنا في المقبرة، والآن نحن هنا، والآن الصباح.
How the hell did that happen?
كيف حدث ذلك بحق الجحيم؟
You broke the Raven's gaze.
لقد كسرت نظرة الغراب.
Now it's playing a dirty trick.
الآن يلعب خدعة قذرة.
How do we swap back?
كيف يمكننا التبديل مرة أخرى؟
You always think you're the smartest person in the room.
تعتقد دائمًا أنك الشخص الأكثر ذكاءً في الغرفة.
I'll let you figure that one out.
سأترك لك معرفة ذلك.
Wednesday?
الأربعاء؟
Who are you talking to?
من الذي تتحدث معه؟
Obviously, it's me. Keep up.
من الواضح أنني أنا. استمر.
Okay, whatever you did, you need to fix it. Right frickin' now!
حسنًا، مهما فعلت، عليك إصلاحه. الآن!
None of this would've happened if you'd left me alone.
لم يكن أي من هذا ليحدث لو تركتني وحدي.
You're seriously blaming me?
هل أنت تلومني حقًا؟
[Enid whimpers]
[تئن إينيد]
I feel so cold and uncomfortable.
أشعر بالبرد وعدم الارتياح.
It's probably your factory setting.
ربما يكون هذا هو إعداد المصنع الخاص بك.
- And I'm warm and clammy. - Werewolves run hot.
- وأنا دافئ ورطب. - الذئاب الضارية ساخنة.
We're hot-blooded creatures.
نحن مخلوقات ذوات الدم الحار.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
يا إلهي، يا إلهي، يا إلهي!
Watching my body contort to your emotional outbursts is making me queasy.
إن مشاهدة جسدي يتشوه بسبب انفعالاتك العاطفية تجعلني أشعر بالغثيان.
Nobody can see us like this, okay?
لا أحد يستطيع رؤيتنا بهذه الطريقة، حسنًا؟
We'll pretend we have a contagious disease,
سنتظاهر بأن لدينا مرضًا معديًا،
and say we need to be quarantined.
ونقول أننا بحاجة إلى الحجر الصحي.
[wry musical flourish]
[ازدهار موسيقي ساخر]
You are not walking out this door.
أنت لا تخرج من هذا الباب.
I'm going back to Rotwood's grave.
سأعود إلى قبر روتوود.
Wednesday?
الأربعاء؟
I'm scared.
أنا خائفة.
- You will get your body back. - Promise?
- سوف تستعيد جسدك. - وعد؟
[whimpers]
[يئن]
[Enid] What are we gonna do?
[إينيد] ماذا سنفعل؟
We tell absolutely no one.
نحن لا نقول لأحد على الإطلاق.
This must remain our secret.
يجب أن يبقى هذا سرنا.
You need to stay away from Bruno.
يجب عليك البقاء بعيدًا عن برونو.
And you must avoid my family at all costs.
ويجب عليك تجنب عائلتي بأي ثمن.
Especially my mother.
وخاصة والدتي.
We got this, right?
لقد حصلنا على هذا، أليس كذلك؟
I mean, how hard is it to act like Wednesday Addams?
أعني، ما مدى صعوبة التصرف مثل وينزداي آدامز؟
[droll, macabre music playing]
[موسيقى مرحة ومرعبة تعزف]
[Bianca] Enid!
[بيانكا] إينيد!
Over here. Saved you a seat.
هنا. حجزت لك مقعدًا.
Coming, guys!
قادمون يا شباب!
[wry, perplexing music playing]
[عزف موسيقى ساخرة ومحيرة]
Get coffee. Sit alone.
أحضر قهوة، واجلس بمفردك.
Stay out of trouble.
ابتعد عن المشاكل.
I'll be back soon.
سأعود قريبا.
Hmm.
همم.
Your braids are fire, Elise.
ضفائرك نار، إليز.
And those shoes are a vibe, Sophia.
وهذه الأحذية لها إحساس رائع، صوفيا.
Way to go, you little psycho.
أحسنت، أيها الصغير المريض.
I was just delivering your morning coffee like I always do.
لقد كنت أقدم لك قهوة الصباح كما أفعل دائمًا.
You do?
أنت تفعل؟
I mean...
أعني...
Right. Of course.
صواب. بالطبع.
I haven't been able to locate Isaac Night's student files yet.
لم أتمكن من العثور على ملفات الطالب إسحاق نايت حتى الآن.
Who's Isaac Night?
من هو اسحق نايت؟
Pugsley's zombie.
زومبي بوغسلي.
[gasps] Duh! Right. I'm clearly suffering from extreme caffeine deprivation.
[يلهث] آه! صحيح. من الواضح أنني أعاني من نقص حاد في الكافيين.
A rainbow furracino with an extra squirt of steak sauce, please.
فوراسينو قوس قزح مع رشة إضافية من صلصة اللحم، من فضلك.
[quizzical musical flourish]
[ازدهار موسيقي غريب]
[dryly] I can tattoo my order on your forehead if that would help.
[بشكل جاف] يمكنني أن أقوم برسم طلبي على جبهتك إذا كان ذلك سيساعد.
I thought you were allergic to color.
اعتقدت أنك تعاني من حساسية تجاه الألوان.
I mean, I just say that to keep up the whole
أعني، أنا أقول هذا فقط للحفاظ على كل شيء
tragic loner, goth girl aesthetic.
فتاة انفرادية مأساوية، ذات طابع قوطي جمالي.
I'll catch you later. Or never.
سألتقي بك لاحقًا. أو لن ألتقي بك أبدًا.
[quirky music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى غريبة]
[serene notes playing]
[نغمات هادئة تعزف]
[gulps, sighs in satisfaction]
[يبتلع، يتنهد في رضا]
[suspenseful music pulsing]
[موسيقى مشوقة نابضة بالحياة]
Whoa, whoa. Enid, wait.
واو، واو. إينيد، انتظري.
It's me.
هذا أنا.
[dour music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى كئيبة]
You said you loved it when I surprised you.
قلت أنك أحببته عندما فاجأتك.
Try again and I'll treat you to some real pain and suffering.
حاول مرة أخرى وسأعالجك ببعض الألم والمعاناة الحقيقية.
[slurping loudly]
[يرتشف بصوت عالٍ]
[tense music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى متوترة]
[gasps]
[تلهث]
This is insane!
هذا جنون!
I was actually allergic to color.
لقد كنت في الواقع مصابًا بحساسية تجاه الألوان.
Wednesday.
الأربعاء.
[shakily] I kinda can't talk right now.
[بصوت مرتجف] لا أستطيع التحدث الآن.
Oh, dear.
يا عزيزي.
I haven't seen your skin break out like that
لم أرى بشرتك تتشقق هكذا
since Pugsley colored the inside of your favorite death mask.
منذ أن قام Pugsley بتلوين الجزء الداخلي من قناع الموت المفضل لديك.
Hmm. I have just the remedy.
مممم. لدي العلاج.
[dour, uneasy music playing]
[موسيقى كئيبة وغير مريحة تعزف]
Wow!
رائع!
This cream is amazing.
هذا الكريم مذهل.
- What's in it? - Beeswax, stinging nettles, and ash.
- ماذا يوجد بداخله؟ - شمع العسل، نبات القراص، والرماد.
Ash?
رماد؟
Scraped from the bottom of a crematorium furnace.
تم كشطها من أسفل فرن حرق الجثث.
One of your grandmama's beauty secrets.
أحد أسرار جمال جدتك.
Although it does give your skin that wonderful corpse-like glow.
على الرغم من أنه يعطي بشرتك ذلك التوهج الرائع الذي يشبه الجثة.
Well...
حسنًا...
Thanks, Mom.
شكرا أمي.
Mom?
أم؟
That's new.
هذا جديد.
Hmm. Something's different about you today.
مممم، هناك شيء مختلف فيك اليوم.
I can see it in your eyes.
أستطيع أن أرى ذلك في عينيك.
It's like your spirit is lighter.
يبدو الأمر وكأن روحك أصبحت أخف.
Well, I'm just trying to embrace my inevitable decay
حسنًا، أنا فقط أحاول احتضان تدهوري الحتمي
with a touch of enthusiasm.
مع لمسة من الحماس.
Why didn't you take your umbra mushroom pills?
لماذا لم تتناول حبوب فطر أومبرا؟
You know you run the risk of an allergic reaction if you skip a day.
أنت تعلم أنك معرض لخطر الإصابة برد فعل تحسسي إذا تخطيت يومًا واحدًا.
Oh. Right.
اوه. صحيح.
My prescription ran out.
انتهت الوصفة الطبية الخاصة بي.
Well, luckily, I stopped by the apothecary and picked up your refill.
حسنًا، لحسن الحظ، توقفت عند الصيدلي وأخذت عبوة إعادة التعبئة الخاصة بك.
This will clear it right up.
سيؤدي هذا إلى توضيح الأمر على الفور.
Got it. Bye.
فهمت. مع السلامة.
- Since you're turning over a dead leaf... - [gasps]
- بما أنك تقلب ورقة ميتة... - [يشهق]
Perhaps you'd like to come for family dinner at the cottage tonight?
ربما ترغب في الحضور لتناول العشاء العائلي في الكوخ الليلة؟
[chuckling] Oh.
[ضحك] أوه.
Uh, tonight's not great for me.
أوه، الليلة ليست رائعة بالنسبة لي.
Pugsley's coming over.
بوغسلي قادم.
And your father's up from the city,
وأبوك قادم من المدينة،
and you know how much family dinners cool his heart.
وأنت تعرف كم أن عشاء العائلة يبرد قلبه.
I would love to come, Mom.
سأحب أن آتي يا أمي.
I mean, Mother.
أعني، أمي.
But I can't.
ولكنني لا أستطيع.
Principal Dort just issued a curfew.
أصدر مدير المدرسة دورث للتو حظرًا للتجوال.
Well, I've already spoken to him,
حسنًا، لقد تحدثت معه بالفعل،
and he's given you and Pugsley a pass for tonight.
وقد أعطاك أنت وبوغسلي تصريحًا الليلة.
Isn't that wonderful?
أليس هذا رائعا؟
Lurch will pick you up at 7:00.
سوف يأتي لورش ليلتقطك في الساعة 7:00.
Don't be late.
لا تتأخر.
[cheekily distraught music playing]
[موسيقى حزينة ومضطربة تعزف]
[groans]
[آهات]
[stifled screaming]
[صراخ مكتوم]
[grimly determined music playing]
[عزف موسيقى مصممة بشكل قاتم]
[Weems] Once again, you have wandered into uncharted territory.
[ويمز] مرة أخرى، لقد تجولت في منطقة مجهولة.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
لا أستطيع أن أقول أنني لم أحذرك.
Fine.
بخير.
How do I undo this?
كيف يمكنني التراجع عن هذا؟
I haven't the foggiest.
ليس لدي الضبابية.
But given my penchant for meticulous research,
ولكن نظرا لميولي نحو البحث الدقيق،
I did discover that two other Ravens
لقد اكتشفت أن اثنين آخرين من الغربان
had the audacity to embark on this foolhardy endeavor before you.
لقد كانت لدي الجرأة للانطلاق في هذا المسعى المتهور قبلك.
- What happened to them? - They were both dead within 24 hours.
- ماذا حدث لهم؟ - لقد مات كلاهما خلال 24 ساعة.
Bravo, Miss Addams.
برافو، الآنسة آدامز.
It appears you'll be responsible for Enid's premature death after all.
يبدو أنك ستكون مسؤولاً عن وفاة إينيد المبكرة بعد كل شيء.
As well as your own.
وكذلك خاصتك.
[harrowing music intensifies]
[تزداد الموسيقى المروعة]
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
[forlorn music playing]
[عزف موسيقى حزينة]
[Isaac scoffs]
[إسحاق يسخر]
- Ready for another one, sweetie? - Mmm.
- هل أنت مستعد لواحدة أخرى يا عزيزتي؟ - ممم.
- Good? - Yeah.
- جيد؟ - نعم.
- Like it? - Better than I remember.
- هل أعجبك؟ - أفضل مما أتذكره.
[Francoise chuckles]
[تضحك فرانسواز]
[rapping at door]
[طرق على الباب]
No, it can't be. It's impossible.
لا، لا يمكن ذلك. هذا مستحيل.
Francoise...
فرانسواز...
Is that any way to greet your brother?
هل هذه طريقة لتحية أخيك؟
You died.
لقد مت.
I held you.
لقد احتضنتك.
In my arms.
بين ذراعي.
Put the gun down.
ضع البندقية جانبا.
Do you remember the Fourth of July?
هل تتذكر الرابع من يوليو؟
Dad caught you with that Normie kid.
لقد أمسكك أبي مع ذلك الطفل النورمي.
Dylan.
ديلان.
He slapped you so hard.
لقد صفعك بقوة.
It was louder than the fireworks.
لقد كان صوته أعلى من الألعاب النارية.
That was the first time you transformed.
لقد كانت هذه المرة الأولى التي تحولت فيها.
[Francoise sobs softly]
[تبكي فرانسواز بهدوء]
I've spent my life dreaming of this moment.
لقد قضيت حياتي أحلم بهذه اللحظة.
Praying that I would see you again.
أدعو الله أن أراك مرة أخرى.
Tyler,
تايلر،
this is your Uncle Isaac.
هذا عمك اسحق.
[Francoise] Mmm.
[فرانسواز] ممم.
[chilling music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مرعبة]
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Tyler.
تايلر.
Nice to meet you.
سعيد بلقائك.
[coughs uncontrollably]
[يسعل بشكل لا يمكن السيطرة عليه]
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
[Francoise breathes heavily]
[فرانسواز تتنفس بصعوبة]
It's our condition.
إنها حالتنا.
Being a Hyde.
كونك هايد.
I've lived longer than most.
لقد عشت أطول من معظم الناس.
[Isaac] I could still help you.
[إسحاق] لا يزال بإمكاني مساعدتك.
It was always my dream.
لقد كان حلمي دائما.
To slay the monster inside you.
لتقتل الوحش بداخلك.
I only need the right equipment.
أحتاج فقط إلى المعدات المناسبة.
Resources.
موارد.
Dr. Stonehurst stole your diaries.
لقد سرق الدكتور ستونهورست مذكراتك.
And he's built a version of your machine at Willow Hill.
وقد بنى نسخة من جهازك في ويلو هيل.
But he perverted it to give our abilities to Normies.
لكنّه حرّفها ليمنح قدراتنا إلى الأشخاص العاديين.
His daughter Judi, she's carrying on his research.
ابنته جودي، تواصل أبحاثه.
She's been hunting me.
لقد كانت تطاردني.
Well,
حسنًا،
Judi...
المقامرة...
retired.
متقاعد.
Permanently.
دائمًا.
[Francoise laughing]
[فرانسواز تضحك]
If that machine exists,
إذا كانت هذه الآلة موجودة،
I can save you.
انا استطيع انقاذك
[Tyler] You can't be serious.
[تايلر] لا يمكنك أن تكون جادًا.
You want to go back to Willow Hill? The place we all just escaped from?
هل ترغب بالعودة إلى ويلو هيل؟ المكان الذي هربنا منه جميعًا؟
[Isaac] Yes, I do.
[إسحاق] نعم أفعل.
But, first, I need to visit an old friend...
لكن، أولاً، أريد أن أزور صديقًا قديمًا...
at Nevermore.
في نيفرمور.
[cello cover of Blue Oyster Cult's "Don't Fear the Reaper" playing]
[عزف على آلة التشيلو لأغنية "Don't Fear the Reaper" لفرقة Blue Oyster Cult]
[Wednesday stops playing]
[توقف اللعب يوم الاربعاء]
Enid?
إينيد؟
Why didn't you tell me you played?
لماذا لم تخبرني أنك لعبت؟
I only do it when I need to think.
أنا أفعل ذلك فقط عندما أحتاج إلى التفكير.
Sounds like you're channeling your inner Wednesday.
يبدو أنك تستحضر يوم الأربعاء الداخلي لديك.
You have no idea.
ليس لديك أي فكرة.
We need to talk about your situation.
نحن بحاجة إلى التحدث عن حالتك.
My situation?
حالتي؟
Denial isn't going to change it.
إن الإنكار لن يغير الأمر.
And there are added risks for a potential Alpha
وهناك مخاطر إضافية لـ "ألفا" المحتملة
in their first lunar cycle.
في دورتهم القمرية الأولى.
Alpha.
ألفا.
Right.
يمين.
Better get to the Lupin cages before sundown. Just play it safe.
من الأفضل الوصول إلى أقفاص لوبين قبل غروب الشمس. فقط كن حذرًا.
I know you're worried about being a lone wolf,
أعلم أنك قلق بشأن كونك ذئبًا منفردًا،
but we need to know what we're dealing with first.
ولكننا نحتاج إلى معرفة ما نتعامل معه أولاً.
[suspenseful music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مشوقة]
[Wednesday] This is Rosaline Rotwood.
[الأربعاء] هذه روزالين روتوود.
[Capri] Professor Orloff said she used to teach in this room back in the day--
[كابري] قالت الأستاذة أورلوف إنها اعتادت أن تدرس في هذه الغرفة في الماضي-
And lived in my mother's cottage.
وعاش في كوخ أمي.
[Capri] What?
[كابري] ماذا؟
[Wednesday] I mean, Mrs. Addams.
[الأربعاء] أعني السيدة آدامز.
In fact, I promised I would drop by for tea this afternoon.
في الواقع، لقد وعدت بأن أمر هنا لشرب الشاي بعد الظهر.
I'm already running late.
لقد تأخرت بالفعل.
[Capri] Make it quick.
[كابري] اجعلها سريعة.
I want you locked in the Lupin cages by sundown.
أريدك أن تكون محبوسًا في أقفاص لوبين عند غروب الشمس.
Mother...
الأم...
Mrs. Addams?
السيدة آدامز؟
[fixture clinks]
[رنين التثبيت]
How could my mother read this drivel?
كيف استطاعت أمي أن تقرأ هذا الهراء؟
[disembodied voice whispering] Wednesday...
[صوت غير مجسد يهمس] الأربعاء...
[jarring stinger]
[لاذعة مزعجة]
Reckless child.
طفل متهور.
Tell me how I can break this curse.
أخبرني كيف يمكنني كسر هذه اللعنة.
To reclaim your own flesh you must be willing to die in this borrowed skin.
لاستعادة جسدك يجب أن تكون على استعداد للموت بهذا الجلد المستعار.
You have until dawn to unravel the innermost secrets
لديك حتى الفجر لكشف الأسرار العميقة
of the life you've stepped into.
من الحياة التي دخلتها.
[Morticia] Enid Sinclair.
[مورتيشيا] إينيد سينكلير.
What are you doing in here snooping around?
ماذا تفعل هنا وتتجسس؟
How dare you?
كيف تجرؤ؟
Mrs. Addams.
السيدة آدامز.
These books...
هذه الكتب...
Did you write these?
هل كتبت هذه؟
That's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
It's just Wednesday's never mentioned it.
إنه مجرد يوم الأربعاء ولم يتم ذكر ذلك مطلقًا.
Well, there are many parts of my life I don't share with my daughter,
حسنًا، هناك العديد من أجزاء حياتي التي لا أشاركها مع ابنتي،
and I'd like to keep it that way.
وأود أن أبقي الأمر على هذا النحو.
Wednesday put you up to this, didn't she?
لقد دفعتك الأربعاء إلى هذا، أليس كذلك؟
Hmm? Is this another attempt to regain her ability?
هممم؟ هل هذه محاولة أخرى لاستعادة قدرتها؟
Snooping around Rotwood's musty seance chamber?
التجسس حول غرفة جلسة روتوود العفنة؟
You can tell Wednesday we'll discuss this at dinner tonight.
يمكنك أن تقول يوم الأربعاء أننا سوف نناقش هذا الأمر على العشاء الليلة.
You can go now.
يمكنك الذهاب الآن.
[Enid] I barely survived a conversation with Mrs. Addams.
لقد نجوت بالكاد من محادثة مع السيدة آدامز.
She'll see right through me. You need to come.
ستفهمني جيدًا. عليك أن تأتي.
You're going to a support group?
هل ستذهب إلى مجموعة دعم؟
"Some of your parts. We help make you feel whole again."
"بعض أجزائك. نساعدك على الشعور بالاكتمال مجددًا."
If anyone knows what it feels like to not feel whole today, it's me.
إذا كان هناك أي شخص يعرف ما هو شعور عدم الشعور بالاكتمال اليوم، فهو أنا.
[determined sigh] Well, if I have to go,
[تنهد مصمم] حسنًا، إذا كان علي أن أذهب،
I need to find some Addams intel.
أحتاج إلى العثور على بعض المعلومات الاستخباراتية حول آدامز.
Wednesday's novel.
رواية الاربعاء.
How bad can it be?
ما مدى سوء الأمر؟
[Enid humming]
[إينيد تدندن]
Evelyn. [chuckles]
إيفلين. [تضحك]
That's the character who's based off me, right?
هذه هي الشخصية التي تستند إليّ، أليس كذلك؟
"A trend-chasing, rainbow-loving, social media addict,
"مُحب لتتبع الاتجاهات، ومُحب لألوان قوس قزح، ومُدمن على وسائل التواصل الاجتماعي،
whose... tastes in clothes and music are a heinous assault on culture"?
"الذين... أذواقهم في الملابس والموسيقى تشكل اعتداءً شنيعًا على الثقافة؟"
"Despite her Lupin abilities, Evelyn is feeble in both body and mind,
"على الرغم من قدراتها مثل لوبين، إلا أن إيفلين ضعيفة جسديًا وعقليًا،
requiring... Viper's pity and protection."
"مطالبة... بالشفقة والحماية من فايبر."
Is this really how Wednesday feels about me?
هل هذا حقا ما يشعر به الأربعاء تجاهي؟
[aching, distraught music playing]
[موسيقى مؤلمة ومضطربة تعزف]
[bold, determined music playing]
[عزف موسيقى جريئة وحازمة]
That's it!
هذا كل شيء!
If Wednesday wants a heinous assault... she's about to get one.
إذا أراد الأربعاء اعتداءً شنيعًا... فهي على وشك الحصول عليه.
["Boombayah" by BLACKPINK playing]
[أغنية "بومبايا" من بلاك بينك تُعزف]
♪ BLACKPINK in your area ♪
♪ بلاك بينك في منطقتك ♪
[BLACKPINK singing in Korean]
[BLACKPINK تغني باللغة الكورية]
Hi!
أهلاً!
What the hell is going on here?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Looks like Wednesday Addams has finally cracked?
يبدو أن Wednesday Addams قد تصدع أخيرًا؟
[shrieking]
[صياح]
[Enid] It's worse than last time!
[إينيد] إنه أسوأ من المرة الماضية!
[restrained seething]
[الغضب المقيد]
[speaking in Tagalog]
[يتحدث باللغة التاغالوغية]
Need to hang up now, my love.
أحتاج إلى إغلاق الهاتف الآن، حبيبتي.
[phone bleeps]
[أصوات الهاتف]
[ominous music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مشؤومة]
Enid. Hey.
إينيد. مرحباً.
I was just talking to my mom in the Philippines.
كنت أتحدث للتو مع والدتي في الفلبين.
You and your mother are awfully close.
أنت وأمك قريبان جدًا.
[in Tagalog] "I miss you."
"افتقدك." [بالتاغالوغية]
"I miss our walks along the beach."
"أفتقد جولاتنا على طول الشاطئ."
"I miss your sweet lips most of all."
"أفتقد شفتيك الحلوة أكثر من أي شيء آخر."
[in English] Or was that your girlfriend you failed to mention
[باللغة الإنجليزية] أم أن تلك كانت صديقتك التي لم تذكرها؟
in an act of time-honored, misogynistic deception?
في عمل من أعمال الخداع المتعارف عليه والكاره للنساء؟
How do you know Tagalog?
كيف تعرف اللغة التاغالوغية؟
I picked it up when I was eight from Datu, my Filipino fencing instructor.
لقد التقطت هذه العبارة عندما كنت في الثامنة من عمري من داتو، مدرب المبارزة الفلبيني الخاص بي.
He also taught me how to castrate with a bolo knife.
لقد علمني أيضًا كيفية الإخصاء بسكين البولو.
I was going to tell you, but it's complicated.
كنت سأخبرك، لكن الأمر معقد.
Then let me uncomplicate it. We're done.
دعني أوضح الأمر. لقد انتهينا.
[in Tagalog] Never talk to me again, you duplicitous Lothario.
[باللغة التاغالوغية]لا تتحدث معي مرة أخرى، أيها الزير المخادع.
[in English] Was that clear enough for you?
[باللغة الإنجليزية] هل كان ذلك واضحا بما فيه الكفاية بالنسبة لك؟
Enid! Lupin cages, now!
إينيد! أقفاص لوبين، الآن!
You're late.
لقد تأخرت.
I can't go. It's a matter of life or death.
لا أستطيع الذهاب. إنها مسألة حياة أو موت.
It could be your life or death if you don't. Come on, come on.
قد تكون حياتك أو موتك إن لم تفعل. هيا، هيا.
[sighs]
[تنهدات]
Hmm.
همم.
[Enid laughs]
[تضحك إينيد]
[Enid whimpering in video]
[إينيد تئن في الفيديو]
So worth it.
إنه يستحق ذلك.
Why are you on Enid's side of the room?
لماذا أنت على جانب إينيد من الغرفة؟
It's none of your business.
هذا ليس من شأنك.
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
As someone who's spent hours obsessively studying you,
كشخص قضى ساعات طويلة في دراستك بشكل مهووس،
I know something's wrong.
أعلم أن هناك شيئًا خاطئًا.
Terribly wrong.
خطأ فظيع.
Your K-pop dance in the Link was clearly a cry for help.
من الواضح أن رقصتك الكورية في الرابط كانت بمثابة صرخة طلبًا للمساعدة.
I'm guessing it's PTSD from your coma.
أعتقد أنها إضطراب ما بعد الصدمة الناتج عن غيبوبتك.
Or maybe even a brain tumor.
أو ربما حتى ورم في المخ.
I'm fine, Agnes.
أنا بخير، أجنيس.
There's no need for concern.
لا داعي للقلق .
You know I prefer to zig when others zag.
أنت تعلم أنني أفضّل أن أسير في طريق متعرج عندما يسلك الآخرون طريقًا متعرجًا.
- [phone bleeps] - [Enid chuckles]
- [أصوات الهاتف] - [تضحك إينيد]
When did you get a phone?
متى حصلت على الهاتف؟
[Enid] Uh...
[إينيد] أوه...
It's Enid's.
إنها إينيد.
She left it behind.
لقد تركتها خلفها.
Huh.
هاه.
No electronics in the Lupin cages.
لا يوجد إلكترونيات في أقفاص لوبين.
It's probably smart.
ربما يكون ذكيا.
No one wants their wolfing out pics going viral.
لا أحد يريد أن تصبح صوره التي يتناولها من الطعام فيروسية.
Why would she be in the Lupin cages?
لماذا هي موجودة في أقفاص لوبين؟
There's not a full moon.
ليس هناك قمر مكتمل.
Capri stuck her in there. Right after she broke up with Bruno.
كابري حطتها هناك. بعد انفصالها عن برونو مباشرةً.
Dumped that dumb dog like yesterday's kitty litter.
تخلصت من هذا الكلب الغبي مثل فضلات القطط أمس.
She broke up with Bruno?
هل انفصلت عن برونو؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Tell me right now, you creepy little creeper!
أخبرني الآن، أيها الزاحف الصغير المخيف!
Why do you care about her overheated YA werewolf drama?
لماذا تهتم بدراما الذئبة الشبابية المحمومة؟
If Enid knew you were trying to keep her from dying,
إذا علمت إينيد أنك تحاول منعها من الموت،
then she might have something to howl about.
ثم قد يكون لديها شيء لتصرخ من أجله.
What do you mean, try to keep her from dying?
ماذا تقصد بمحاولة منعها من الموت؟
Your premonition... of course.
حدسك... بالطبع.
[Enid] Oh...
[إينيد] أوه...
I can't believe she would do this to me.
لا أستطيع أن أصدق أنها تفعل هذا بي.
I'm starting to think Enid is the problem.
بدأت أعتقد أن إينيد هي المشكلة.
Your obsession with saving her has caused you to crack.
إن هوسك بإنقاذها قد تسبب في انهيارك.
- Oof. - Who can blame you?
- اووف. - من يستطيع أن يلومك؟
Living with a clueless, boy-crazy cliché like Enid Sinclair.
العيش مع فتاة جاهلة ومهووسة بالأولاد مثل إينيد سنكلير.
It's enough to put anyone in a straitjacket.
إنه كافٍ لوضع أي شخص في سترة مقيدة.
Maybe it's time to cut her off.
ربما حان الوقت لقطعها.
Like a bad finger.
مثل إصبع سيء.
I'm certainly more than ready to be best friends with you.
أنا بالتأكيد أكثر من مستعد لأن أكون أفضل صديق لك.
You don't know anything about me.
أنت لا تعرف شيئا عني.
You're just a sycophantic loser that I use when it's convenient.
أنت مجرد خاسر متملق أستخدمه عندما يكون ذلك مناسبًا.
But we're not friends.
ولكننا لسنا أصدقاء.
I don't even like you.
انا لا احبك حتى.
In fact, I wish you would just stay invisible.
في الواقع، أتمنى أن تبقى غير مرئي.
Forever!
للأبد!
[door opens]
[يفتح الباب]
[breathing unevenly]
[التنفس بشكل غير متساوٍ]
[Orloff] As you may have heard, Lisa is no longer in our group.
[أورلوف] كما سمعتم، ليزا لم تعد في مجموعتنا.
She's been reunited with her torso.
لقد تم لم شملها مع جذعها.
We all support her decision.
نحن جميعا ندعم قرارها.
But remember,
ولكن تذكر،
we are whole,
نحن كاملون
just the way we are.
كما نحن.
[Agnes] Excuse me, I...
[أغنيس] عذراً، أنا...
Sorry to interrupt.
عذرا على المقاطعة.
I know I'm not technically a body part,
أعلم أنني لست جزءًا من الجسم من الناحية الفنية،
but... the sign said, "All are welcome."
لكن... اللافتة تقول "الجميع مرحب بهم".
And they are.
وهم كذلك.
So please, share whatever's on your mind.
لذا من فضلك، شاركنا بكل ما يجول في ذهنك.
I thought at Nevermore,
اعتقدت في نيفرمور،
I would finally be seen.
سوف يتم رؤيتي أخيرا.
[gentle, aching music playing]
[موسيقى لطيفة ومؤلمة تعزف]
Have real friends.
لدي أصدقاء حقيقيين.
But the truth is,
ولكن الحقيقة هي
I feel more invisible than ever.
أشعر بأنني غير مرئية أكثر من أي وقت مضى.
We want you to know that we all see you, Agnes.
نريدك أن تعلم أننا جميعًا نراك، أغنيس.
Make yourself at home.
البيت بيتك.
We have another newbie.
لدينا مبتدئ آخر.
Welcome, Thing.
مرحباً بك، شيء.
What would you like to share with the group?
ماذا تريد أن تشاركه مع المجموعة؟
You don't have any idea where you came from?
ليس لديك أي فكرة من أين أتيت؟
When you were found by the Addams family,
عندما تم العثور عليك من قبل عائلة آدامز،
the only clue to your past was a silver signet ring.
الدليل الوحيد على ماضيك كان خاتمًا فضيًا.
Well, you're fortunate to have people who care about you.
حسنًا، أنت محظوظ لأن لديك أشخاصًا يهتمون بك.
We may never know who we were attached to.
ربما لن نعرف أبدًا من كنا مرتبطين به.
You can't see yourself as an appendage,
لا يمكنك أن ترى نفسك كملحق،
but as a whole person,
ولكن كشخص كامل،
worthy of love and respect.
جدير بالحب والاحترام.
We are more than just the sum of our parts.
نحن أكثر من مجرد مجموع أجزائنا.
But sometimes,
ولكن في بعض الأحيان،
the parts are greater than the whole.
الأجزاء أكبر من الكل.
- [Morticia gasps] - [Gomez] Yes!
- [تشهق مورتيشيا] - [جوميز] نعم!
Bravo, Lurch.
برافو، لورش.
You have outdone yourself.
لقد تفوقت على نفسك.
[Gomez] Mm-hmm.
[جوميز] مممم.
[Enid stifling gag reflex]
[إينيد تخنق رد الفعل المنعكس]
[cheeky, eccentric music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى وقحة وغريبة]
[Morticia] Delicious.
[مورتيشيا] لذيذ.
[Lurch growls]
[هدير لورش]
Mmm.
ممم.
Ooh, wow.
أوه، واو.
Yes.
نعم.
[disgusted yelp]
[صرخة اشمئزاز]
Remind me what this is again?
أذكرني ما هذا مرة أخرى؟
Darling, don't you recognize your favorite family dish?
عزيزتي، هل لا تتعرفين على الطبق العائلي المفضل لديك؟
- Roadkill pot pie. - [Morticia] Mm-hmm.
- فطيرة وعاء Roadkill. - [مورتيسيا] مم-هم.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Yum!
لذيذ!
- What's in it? - [Gomez] Possum.
- ماذا يوجد بداخله؟ - [جوميز] بوسوم.
Little guy ran out right in front of us.
الرجل الصغير ركض أمامنا مباشرة.
Lurch backed up over it twice.
تراجع لورش مرتين.
Tenderized it. Ooh, yeah.
لقد طريته. أوه، نعم.
He also added a little leftover raccoon,
وأضاف أيضًا القليل من بقايا الراكون،
which gives that special woodsy flavor you adore.
الذي يعطي تلك النكهة الخشبية الخاصة التي تعشقها.
[weakly] Mmm.
[ضعيفًا] ممم.
[glass clinking]
[رنين الزجاج]
[Lurch groans]
[تأوه لورش]
Now that we're all here together, it's time for a serious discussion.
الآن بعد أن أصبحنا جميعًا هنا معًا، فقد حان الوقت لإجراء مناقشة جادة.
Your father and I have tried to instill our family values in you children.
لقد حاولنا أنا ووالدكم غرس قيمنا العائلية في أطفالكم.
But we draw the line on lying.
لكننا نضع حدًا للكذب.
I thought you said lying was an important life skill.
اعتقدت أنك قلت أن الكذب مهارة حياتية مهمة.
Yes, like in business, politics,
نعم، كما هو الحال في الأعمال والسياسة،
jury duty... that's a big one.
واجب هيئة المحلفين... هذا أمر كبير.
You two have been lying to us.
لقد كنتما تكذبان علينا.
And I'll give you one chance to confess.
وسأعطيك فرصة واحدة للاعتراف.
- There's still a punishment, right? - Of course. Don't be silly.
- لا يزال هناك عقاب، صحيح؟ - بالطبع. لا تكن سخيفًا.
I lied to you about Slurp.
لقد كذبت عليك بشأن سلورب.
I saw him at Pilgrim World, and I let him go.
رأيته في عالم الحجاج، وتركته يذهب.
I'm really sorry, Pop.
أنا آسف حقا يا أبي.
So, um...
إذن، أم...
do I get the rack or iron maiden?
هل أحصل على الرف أو العذراء الحديدية؟
We'll flip for it.
سوف نقلب من أجله.
Come on. Let's go.
هيا، لنذهب.
Please excuse us.
أرجو المعذرة.
You ladies enjoy dinner.
سيداتي، استمتعوا بالعشاء.
Earlier, I caught Enid in Rosaline Rotwood's secret seance chamber.
في وقت سابق، تمكنت من القبض على إينيد في غرفة جلسة روزالين روتوود السرية.
Any idea why she was snooping?
هل لديك أي فكرة لماذا كانت تتجسس؟
None, actually.
لا يوجد في الواقع.
Hmm.
همم.
I see that bewildered look in your eyes.
أرى تلك النظرة الحائرة في عينيك.
It's the same look I noticed this morning.
إنه نفس الشكل الذي لاحظته هذا الصباح.
- [Enid whimpers] - And now it makes sense.
- [تئن إينيد] - والآن أصبح الأمر منطقيًا.
Your obsession for getting your ability back
هوسك باستعادة قدرتك
has finally made you lose your mind.
لقد جعلك تفقد عقلك أخيرًا.
What?
ماذا؟
But don't worry.
ولكن لا تقلق.
I will have Lurch make up the guest room.
سأطلب من لورش أن يقوم بتجهيز غرفة الضيوف.
No, that... that... that really isn't necessary.
لا، هذا... هذا... هذا ليس ضروريًا حقًا.
I sense your presence again. Show yourself.
أشعر بوجودك مرة أخرى. أظهر نفسك.
I demand it.
انا اطالب بذلك.
You're still as insufferably bossy as you were in 10th grade.
مازلت متسلطًا بشكل لا يطاق كما كنت في الصف العاشر.
Larissa?
لاريسا؟
- Who's Larissa? - Shh!
- من هي لاريسا؟ - ششش!
Morticia, it's good to see you.
مورتيشيا، من الجميل رؤيتك.
Oh, I just remembered. I--
أوه، لقد تذكرت للتو. أنا--
Sit down.
اجلس.
I am Wednesday's new spirit guide.
أنا الدليل الروحي الجديد يوم الاربعاء.
Wait.
انتظر.
If you're her guide, why can't she see you?
إذا كنت مرشدها، فلماذا لا تستطيع رؤيتك؟
[Weems] At your beloved mother's suggestion,
[ويمز] بناء على اقتراح والدتك الحبيبة،
Wednesday attempted to gain temporary second sight
حاول الأربعاء الحصول على رؤية ثانية مؤقتة
at Rosaline Rotwood's headstone.
عند شاهدة قبر روزالين روتوود.
That's why she dispatched Enid to search for answers
لهذا السبب أرسلت إينيد للبحث عن الإجابات
in Rotwood's seance chamber.
في غرفة جلسة روتوود.
Except that wasn't Enid.
إلا أن هذه لم تكن إينيد.
It was Wednesday.
وكان يوم الاربعاء.
Enid?
إينيد؟
Is that you in there?
هل أنت هناك؟
Where's Wednesday?
أين الأربعاء؟
Locked in the Lupin cages until the morning.
محبوسين في أقفاص اللوبين حتى الصباح.
It'll be too late.
سيكون الوقت متأخرا جدا.
They only have until dawn to set this right.
ليس لديهم سوى الوقت حتى الفجر لتصحيح هذا الأمر.
We can't help them, Morticia.
نحن لا نستطيع مساعدتهم، مورتيشيا.
They have to save themselves.
عليهم أن ينقذوا أنفسهم.
Mrs. Addams, I--
السيدة آدامز، أنا--
You must free Wednesday and fix this together before dawn.
يجب عليك تحرير يوم الأربعاء وإصلاح هذا الأمر معًا قبل الفجر.
That's your only chance.
هذه فرصتك الوحيدة .
[grim, distressing music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى قاتمة ومزعجة]
[wheels buzzing]
[عجلات طنين]
[Isaac] I hope I'm not late for the meeting.
[إسحاق] أتمنى ألا أتأخر عن الاجتماع.
Hello, Professor.
مرحباً أستاذ.
[shocked gasp]
[شهقة مصدومة]
Don't you recognize your star student?
هل لا تتعرف على الطالب المتميز لديك؟
It can't be.
لا يمكن أن يكون.
Isaac Night disappeared
اختفى إسحاق نايت
30 years ago.
منذ 30 عامًا.
Correction, Professor. I died 30 years ago.
تصحيح يا أستاذ، لقد توفيت منذ 30 عامًا.
Never underestimate the power of science.
لا تقلل أبدًا من قوة العلم.
Isn't that what you told me?
أليس هذا ما قلته لي؟
Science has nothing to do with it.
ليس للعلم علاقة بالأمر.
You're a perversion of nature.
أنت انحراف عن الطبيعة.
Says the talking head in a jar.
يقول الرأس المتكلم في جرة.
But you're only alive...
ولكنك على قيد الحياة فقط...
because of me.
بسببي.
[chilling music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مرعبة]
My invention has given you 30 years of borrowed time.
لقد أعطاك اختراعي 30 عامًا من الوقت المستعار.
[gears whirring frantically]
[تروس تدور بشكل محموم]
And now I've come to collect.
والآن جئت لأجمع.
Isaac! Don't!
إسحاق! لا تفعل!
No! Stop!
لا! توقف!
Isaac!
إسحاق!
[energy crackles]
[طاقة طقطقة]
[Orloff straining]
[أورلوف يجهد]
Don't worry, Professor.
لا تقلق يا أستاذ.
I wouldn't let such a great mind go to waste.
لن أسمح لمثل هذا العقل العظيم أن يضيع.
[chilling music intensifies]
[تزداد الموسيقى المرعبة]
[wet crunching, smacking in distance]
[طحن مبلل، صفعة في المسافة]
[shrieks]
[يصرخ]
[jarring stinger]
[لاذعة مزعجة]
[breathing shakily]
[يتنفس بصعوبة]
- [Isaac chuckles] - [Francoise] Mmm.
- [يضحك إسحاق] - [فرانسواز] مممم.
What is that?
ما هذا؟
A power source for the machine at Willow Hill.
مصدر الطاقة للآلة في ويلو هيل.
Since their whole electrical system was fried.
منذ أن تم تفجير نظامهم الكهربائي بأكمله .
[bird cawing in distance]
[نعيق الطائر في المسافة]
[sinister music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى شريرة]
[whispers] Tyler.
[همس] تايلر.
Check outside.
التحقق من الخارج.
[faint thud]
[صوت مكتوم خافت]
[jolting stinger]
[لسعة صادمة]
[gasps softly]
[يتنهد بهدوء]
Okay?
تمام؟
- It's nothing. - Okay.
- لا شيء. - حسنًا.
Seat belts.
حزام الامان.
Tyler.
تايلر.
Your little creeper told me about your vision of my death.
لقد أخبرني زاحفك الصغير عن رؤيتك لموتي.
Thanks for the trust.
شكرا على الثقة.
I also know that if we don't switch back by dawn,
وأعلم أيضًا أنه إذا لم نعد إلى وضعنا السابق عند الفجر،
we're both going to die.
نحن الاثنان سوف نموت
And I am not checking out looking like this.
وأنا لا أتطلع إلى المظهر مثل هذا.
[phone buzzing]
[رنين الهاتف]
[Enid huffs]
[إنيد تنهد]
[phone bleeps]
[أصوات الهاتف]
[Agnes] Wednesday... I know we currently aren't friends,
[أغنيس] الأربعاء... أعلم أننا لسنا أصدقاء حاليًا،
but I found them.
ولكنني وجدتهم.
I found Tyler Galpin and Isaac Night.
لقد وجدت تايلر جالبين وإيزاك نايت.
I took a leaf out of your detecting playbook.
لقد أخذت ورقة من كتاب الكشف الخاص بك.
I'm currently hiding in their trunk along with a very...
أنا أختبئ حاليًا في صندوقهم جنبًا إلى جنب مع ...
very dead body.
جثة ميتة جداً.
At least somebody stayed on task.
على الأقل بقي شخص ما في مهمته.
Agnes, are you insane? Get the hell out of there!
أغنيس، هل أنتِ مجنونة؟ ابتعدي عن هنا!
No.
لا.
It's too late.
لقد فات الأوان.
Sharing my location with you now.
أشارك موقعي معك الآن.
[phone beeping]
[صوت صفير الهاتف]
- They're headed to Willow Hill. - We need to switch back.
- إنهم متجهون إلى ويلو هيل. - نحن بحاجة إلى التبديل مرة أخرى.
After we save Agnes and take down the Galpins.
بعد أن أنقذنا أغنيس وهزمنا الجالبينز.
[music fades]
[تتلاشى الموسيقى]
[energy humming]
[طنين الطاقة]
I can finally keep that promise I made to you.
أستطيع أخيرًا الوفاء بالوعد الذي قطعته لك.
- [Francoise, fondly] Hmm. - To free you from this horrible curse.
- [فرانسواز، بحنان] همم. - لتحريرك من هذه اللعنة الرهيبة.
[Isaac] Here.
[إسحاق] هنا.
- We have to secure you for the procedure. - Yeah.
- علينا أن نؤمنك لإجراء العملية. - نعم.
You think being a Hyde is a curse?
هل تعتقد أن كونك هايد هو لعنة؟
It's the most free I've ever felt.
لقد كان هذا هو الشعور الأكثر حرية الذي شعرت به على الإطلاق.
[Francoise] That so-called freedom comes at a price.
[فرانسواز] إن ما يسمى بالحرية له ثمن.
Every transformation has a human cost.
كل تحول له تكلفة إنسانية.
Until it finally steals your life.
حتى أنه في النهاية يسرق حياتك.
I designed this machine to remove Outcast abilities.
لقد صممت هذه الآلة لإزالة قدرات المنبوذين.
If I can take away your mother's Hyde side,
إذا كان بإمكاني أن أزيل جانب هايد من والدتك،
I can stop her from dying.
أستطيع أن أمنعها من الموت.
[phone bleeps]
[أصوات الهاتف]
[faint clink in distance]
[رنين خافت في المسافة]
Someone else is here.
هناك شخص آخر هنا.
[Isaac] Uh...
[إسحاق] أوه...
[Agnes gasps]
[تنهد أغنيس]
Little snoop is one of Wednesday's friends.
المتطفل الصغير هو أحد أصدقاء الأربعاء.
What do you want me to do with her?
ماذا تريدني أن أفعل بها؟
Put her in a cell.
وضعها في زنزانة.
I'll need a snack once I'm done.
سأحتاج إلى وجبة خفيفة بمجرد الانتهاء.
[Agnes straining]
[أغنيس تجهد]
This way! The lab is through that door.
من هنا! المختبر من خلال هذا الباب.
[Agnes pants] Ah!
[بنطال أغنيس] آه!
[Isaac hums softly]
[يدندن إسحاق بهدوء]
[Tyler] Make yourself at home.
[تايلر] اجعل نفسك في المنزل.
We can deal with that Nevermore brat later.
يمكننا التعامل مع هذا الطفل المشاغب لاحقًا.
[Isaac] Ready, Francoise?
[إسحاق] هل أنت مستعد، فرانسواز؟
[machinery humming]
[طنين الآلات]
Wednesday!
الأربعاء!
[door opens]
[يفتح الباب]
Look who showed up.
انظر من ظهر.
- Don't forget about me. - [Tyler grunts]
- لا تنساني. - [تايلر يتذمر]
- [Wednesday] Leave her alone! - No full moon to save you--
- [الأربعاء] دعها وشأنها! - لا يوجد قمر مكتمل لإنقاذك--
[Tyler grunts]
[تايلر يتذمر]
[panting]
[لهث]
[chains rattling]
[سلاسل تهتز]
[Agnes] Wednesday?
[أغنيس] الأربعاء؟
You need to calm down or you're gonna wolf out.
يجب عليك أن تهدأ وإلا فسوف تصاب بالذئبة.
Too late. Get out!
لقد فات الأوان. اخرج!
[flesh distending, bones cracking]
[تمدد اللحم، وتكسير العظام]
[Wednesday groaning]
[أنين الأربعاء]
[machinery whirring intensifying]
[آلات تهتز وتكثف]
[Isaac sputtering]
[إسحاق يتلعثم]
[exhales] Wednesday.
[يزفر] الأربعاء.
[forceful pounding]
[ضربات قوية]
[pounding continues]
[يستمر الضرب]
[heroic music swelling]
[تضخم الموسيقى البطولية]
[Wednesday snarling]
[زمجرة الأربعاء]
Tyler, no!
تايلر، لا!
Wednesday? Wednesday!
الاربعاء؟ الاربعاء!
Wednesday, we have to go now!
الأربعاء، علينا أن نذهب الآن!
[uncontrollable whirring]
[طنين لا يمكن السيطرة عليه]
[heightened, suspenseful music playing]
[تشغيل موسيقى مشوقة ومرتفعة]
Let's go!
دعنا نذهب!
[Francoise] Go! Gotta get out of here!
[فرانسواز] هيا! عليّ الخروج من هنا!
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
[breathing heavily]
[يتنفس بصعوبة]
[delicate, emotional music playing]
[عزف موسيقى حساسة وعاطفية]
Thank you for saving my life.
شكرا لك على انقاذ حياتي.
I just asked myself, "What would Enid do?"
لقد سألت نفسي للتو، "ماذا ستفعل إينيد؟"
So you guys did swap bodies. I knew something was up.
لقد تبادلتم الأجساد. كنت أعلم أن هناك خطبًا ما.
You've been acting really weird all day.
لقد كنت تتصرف بغرابة طوال اليوم.
And you just called her Wednesday back there, so...
لقد اتصلت بها للتو يوم الأربعاء الماضي، لذا...
we're still friends.
مازلنا أصدقاء.
Well, don't worry. It's okay. It's really hard for me too.
حسنًا، لا تقلق. لا بأس. الأمر صعبٌ عليّ أيضًا.
But we'll get used to this whole new look together.
لكننا سنعتاد على هذا المظهر الجديد معًا.
Not if I can help it. Agnes, go back to Nevermore.
لا، إن استطعتُ. أغنيس، عودي إلى نيفرمور.
Um...
واحد...
Where are we going?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون؟
[grim, imposing music playing]
[عزف موسيقى قاتمة ومهيبة]
Now what?
ماذا الآن؟
Rotwood said we had to unravel
قال روتوود إننا يجب أن نكشف
the innermost secrets of the lives we stepped into.
الأسرار الأعمق للحياة التي دخلناها.
[scoffs] Fine.
[يسخر] حسنًا.
I'll go first.
سأذهب أولا.
You know what I love about being Wednesday?
هل تعلم ما أحبه في يوم الأربعاء؟
Your fearlessness.
شجاعتك.
Except when it comes to your mom. But... I get it.
إلا عندما يتعلق الأمر بأمك. لكن... أفهم ذلك.
[sighs] She can be a lot.
[تنهد] يمكنها أن تكون كثيرة.
You're afraid she'll never accept you for who you truly are.
أنت خائف من أنها لن تقبلك أبدًا كما أنت حقًا.
That your darkness is even too much for her to grasp.
أن ظلامك أكثر مما تستطيع استيعابه.
You'll become the disappointment she'll never want to speak of.
سوف تصبح خيبة الأمل التي لن ترغب في التحدث عنها أبدًا.
Just like your aunt.
تمامًا مثل عمتك.
I can feel it in your bones.
أستطيع أن أشعر به في عظامك.
That's why you push her away.
لهذا السبب تدفعها بعيدا.
But maybe she has more to teach you than you think.
ولكن ربما لديها المزيد لتعليمك إياه مما تعتقد.
[introspective music playing]
[عزف موسيقى تأملية]
The best thing about being Enid is your quiet strength.
أفضل شيء في كونك إينيد هو قوتك الهادئة.
You think being an Alpha will mean you'll be alone.
أنت تعتقد أن كونك ألفا يعني أنك ستكون وحيدًا.
I won't let that happen.
لن اسمح بحدوث ذلك .
You need to stop trying so hard for people who don't deserve it.
يجب عليك التوقف عن المحاولة بكل جهدك من أجل أشخاص لا يستحقون ذلك.
Like Bruno, who mistook your kindness for weakness.
مثل برونو، الذي أخطأ في اعتبار لطفك ضعفًا.
It's not.
ليست كذلك.
It's your power.
إنها قوتك.
Which I could barely handle for one night.
والتي بالكاد تمكنت من التعامل معها لليلة واحدة.
[chuckles softly]
[يضحك بهدوء]
[emotional music building]
[بناء الموسيقى العاطفية]
I regret ever underestimating you.
أنا أأسف على التقليل من شأنك.
[emotional music swells]
[تتضخم الموسيقى العاطفية]
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
Oh my God.
يا إلهي.
Wednesday!
الأربعاء!
We're alive!
نحن على قيد الحياة!
I feel so warm and fuzzy!
أشعر بالدفء والراحة!
And I feel as cold as a cadaver.
وأشعر بالبرد كالجثة.
Which means I'm me and you're you! Ah!
وهذا يعني أنني أنا وأنت أنت! آه!
[jolting stinger]
[لسعة صادمة]
Enid.
إينيد.
Why don't you go back to the dorm and get changed?
لماذا لا تعود إلى السكن وتغير ملابسك؟
I'll be right behind you.
سأكون خلفك مباشرة.
Good idea. I could seriously use a bubble bath.
فكرة جيدة. أحتاج حقًا إلى حمام فقاعات.
[moody, uneasy music playing]
[موسيقى متقلبة وغير مريحة]
The premonition of Enid's imminent death is no more.
لم يعد هناك أي شعور بموت إينيد الوشيك.
So why the dour face?
فلماذا الوجه العابس؟
Your actions today have put another life at risk.
إن أفعالك اليوم قد عرضت حياة أخرى للخطر.
Follow me.
اتبعني.
[birds cawing]
[نعيق الطيور]
[Weems] An Addams must die.
[ويمز] يجب أن يموت آدمز.
The question is...
السؤال هو...
which one?
أيها؟
[moody music intensifying]
[موسيقى مزاجية مكثفة]
[music trails off]
[تتوقف الموسيقى]
[jauntily macabre outro music playing]
[موسيقى خاتمة مرحة ومرعبة تُعزف]